Have you always thought
this was a murder?
You're a former criminal detective.
Having sharp instincts is a good thing.
But Gao Yuhai is a local celebrity.
There are so many eyes on him.
It's fine if you can
get to the bottom of it.
But what if you make a mistake...
Yes, I understand.
I just want to use the tricycle
as a breakthrough.
It's a clue worth investigating.
If it turns out
to be nothing in the end,
I'll accept it.
But what if there is something?
I wouldn't be able to sleep
if I didn't look into it,
and I'd be unworthy of my badge.
Are you trying to investigate Song Yanfei?
Are you sure?
You told me
he was your childhood friend.
Director Wu,
I'm looking for the truth.
It has nothing to do
with anyone
or any friendship.
Remember to report back
if anything comes up.
Then let's talk about
how you met Song Yanfei.
Gao Yayan introduced us.
How did you meet Gao Yayan?
On the street.
Not long after my dad died,
my mom left us.
I heard from the neighbors
that she ran off with a rich guy.
I didn't believe it.
I saw her
when I passed by a hotel that day.
Si,
isn't that your mom?
Why is she here?
Even though the neighbors
gossip about my mom,
deep down,
I always think she's a good person.
Get lost!
My mom would give me
whatever I asked for.
But that day,
it was like she became
a completely different person.
Why are you here?
Who is he?
Let's go outside to talk.
Say it right here.
Tell me,
who is this old man?
Let go of me.
I know who he is now.
My mom followed me out. Si!
I thought she was going
to explain it to me,
Si!
and then come home with me,
and promise me
she'd cut ties
with that old man forever.
Take this money.
To my surprise,
Mom is working. You should leave.
she actually gave me a handful of cash.
I don't want your dirty money!
Just you wait!
I was so depressed that day.
I couldn't figure out
how my mom could really be...
A money-grubber like her...
I made up my mind then
that I'd never see her again,
nor call her mom.
Let her live with that old man.
She can forget about ever
getting close to her son again.
The more I thought about it,
the more depressed I got,
so I shouted at the river to vent.
After I calmed down,
I heard someone talking to me.
Who are you?
Do we know each other?
That day,
I was in no mood to talk to anyone.
Little did I know
we'd run into each other
the very next day.
Drink up.
Don't overthink it.
We're adults now.
Everyone has their own life
to live.
Cheers.
Watch your mouth.
Alright, alright.
Let it go.
Don't pull me.
I'm going out for a bit.
Who are you? What do you want?
You're quite forgetful.
You forgot me already?
What do you want?
I just drank your sweet water.
I'll pay you back.
You're young,
but you have quite a temper.
You didn't look too happy
drinking with your friends in there.
Let's have a drink.
My treat.
Forget it.
I told you last time.
We don't know
each other.
There's
no need.
The man with your mom is my dad.
We're in the same boat.
Let's talk.
Anyway, I just got to know Gao Yayan.
She told me
that although her dad hasn't remarried,
he's been messing around
with a lot of women secretly.
She's on the verge
of cutting ties with him.
I felt we had a lot in common,
so we got to know each other.
Did you interact much?
With Gao Yayan?
Not really.
We only met a few times.
I actually interacted more
with Song Yanfei.
So you met Song Yanfei
and the rest of them that night?
Yeah.
Aren't they dating?
Then tell us the details.
That day, Gao Yayan and I
talked about my mom and her dad.
We talked a lot,
and drank quite a bit too.
Cheers.
Okay,
you're my sister from now on.
If you ever need anything,
I'll risk my life for you.
Okay.
But
I don't need you to risk your life for me.
I just hope you get better and better.
How much did you drink?
Yanfei,
you're here.
Come,
let me introduce you.
This is
Bai Xiaosi.
Just call him Xiaosi.
From today on, he's my brother.
And this is
Song Yanfei.
You can call him
brother-in-law.
Right?
Brother-in-law, what do you do?
Your brother-in-law is a director.
He's amazing.
A director?
Brother-in-law,
can you help me plan
my videos?
Come on, brother-in-law,
I'll drink to that.
Let me tell you,
your videos are nothing to him.
How should I put it?
When he takes action,
everything works out.
Right?
Alright, alright. Come on, cheers.
We're family from now on.
Okay.
Did Song Yanfei ever plan your videos?
Yes, he did.
All my videos
with high views
were planned by him.
So,
the viral video
where you impersonated a traffic cop
was also planned by him, right?
No, it wasn't.
Or
you just don't want to talk?
I guess so.
You guess so?
Just tell the truth.
He lives in a small courtyard
in the suburbs.
I'd go hang out with him when I was free.
That day...
Brother-in-law, I'm here.
Why are you here?
What's up?
Why do you have a broken tricycle here?
What do you mean broken?
It's a souvenir, got it?
A souvenir?
Who collects this junk?
Even scrap dealers wouldn't take it.
One man's meat
is another man's poison.
Don't you get it?
No.
It means
this tricycle might mean
nothing to you,
but to your sister,
it's a souvenir.
And to some people,
it's poison.
Poison?
Isn't that highly toxic?
I think you're highly toxic.
Spit it out.
What do you want?
It's about my videos again.
What?
Wuxia?
Superman?
Cross-dressing,
Disney cartoons,
I've tried them all.
Nothing works.
I've got it all figured out for you.
You
need to think outside the box.
And it has to be realistic.
That sounds solid.
Then tell me,
how is it original and realistic?
Are we talking out here?
Let's go inside.
Isn't it cool?
That's amazing.
So you playing a traffic cop
was what Song Yanfei taught you that day?
Yeah, he told me it would work.
Disguised as a doctor,
a security guard,
and what else...
Anyway, there were four or five of them.
So that day you went
to the bar with Xiao Ze,
you put on that act
in front of him on purpose?
Tell the truth.
I get it now.
This whole case
has nothing to do with you, Bai Xiaosi.
You were just being used, right?
Right. I don't know anything.
Answer me.
Yes or no?
I guess so.
I did receive a call
from Song Yanfei that day.
He told me to go straight to the bar
and pretend to be a traffic cop.
But
whether it had anything
to do with Xiao Ze,
I really don't know.
Hello?
Are you hanging out
with your
cosplay friends tonight?
Yeah, I'm figuring out
what to dress up as.
A traffic cop.
You can
test it out.
I don't really dare to.
What if real cops catch me?
Who told you to wear it outside?
Can't you just bring it
and change at the bar?
Listen to me.
Go as a traffic cop,
and you'll be the coolest guy there.
Makes sense.
I'll definitely turn heads in this.
This is it.
Which bar
are you going to tonight?
Du World. Why?
Du World.
Okay, nothing.
Your sister and I might drop by
if we have time.
But maybe not.
Okay, sure. No problem.
Hey, Xiao Ze.
What are you up to?
Hey,
I'm at home.
I've got some inside information for you.
Shen Xi
is going to a bar
called Du Shijie tonight.
Do you want to go?
Really?
Of course.
But maybe she won't go.
But what if she does?
Right.
What if she does?
I'm hanging up.
I need to get ready.
Thanks.
According to Bai Xiaosi's confession,
Song Yanfei did instruct him
to wear a period costume
and enter the woods
from the east side of the hill
and drop the hemp rope
under the designated crooked tree.
The purpose was
to attract public attention
and become an internet celebrity
if someone secretly filmed him.
It seems
this Song Yanfei
is connected to almost everyone.
Chief Wu,
judging solely from the current situation,
Bai Xiaosi
was only responsible for throwing
the hemp rope into the woods.
As for whether Shen Xi used
the hemp rope to kill Xiao Ze...
Or if Xiao Ze hanged himself
with the hemp rope out of agitation,
we still don't know.
Based on the hemp rope clue,
Song Yanfei doesn't meet
the conditions for a summons.
From another perspective,
if we question him,
there are roughly two scenarios.
The first is that he's actually guilty.
If so,
he would have prepared a perfect story
to deal with us.
Shen Xi is dead,
so we have no way to verify it,
right?
The second scenario is that
he just followed Shen Xi's arrangement
and simply gave him a hemp rope.
Then he would just tell the truth,
and we wouldn't get anything out of him.
Right now,
the task force's opinion is
to not alert the enemy
and look for a breakthrough.
Especially to find out if he and Xiao Ze
knew each other
and what their past was.
Yanfei,
I really feel like
someone is following me.
I'm a little scared.
Are you behind me?
Who are you?
Why are you following her?
I just...
Speak.
No.
Who are you?
Is it any of your business?
Get up.
I'm her brother.
What do you think?
Her brother?
Do you live in this neighborhood?
I live in the building opposite.
If I'm not mistaken,
you can see Shen Xi's rooftop
from your place,
right?
So you like Shen Xi.
You pervert!
There's a small shop outside.
Let's go out and talk about why.
It's nothing. I just like you.
I'll talk to him.
Don't worry.
Then be careful.
Call me anytime.
I'll wait for you.
I don't drink this. Thanks.
You studied dance too?
How did you know?
Just a feeling.
You have a different vibe.
I used to study dance too.
What about now?
Then
my dad wouldn't let me dance anymore.
Why?
My dad said
boys who study this
will have a hard time finding a job.
And it's useless for the family business.
That's absurd.
Since you're so honest,
go ahead.
What do you want to ask?
I'll tell you everything.
Really?
Anything?
Really.
Are you her biological brother?
Cousin.
Do you visit her often?
Occasionally.
My aunt and uncle are
a bit worried about her,
so I come to check on her occasionally.
Did she spot me?
How did she find out about me?
You'll have to
ask yourself that.
Weren't you a bit too amateur at stalking?
Do you know what she told me?
She said a pervert
was stalking her and about to make a move.
That's you, right?
I really didn't mean that.
I just like her,
so I wanted to see her more.
I really didn't mean any harm.
Please help me explain it to her.
Calm down.
If that's the case,
why don't you just confess
your feelings to her?
I'm too scared.
Don't laugh at me, but
when I was studying dance
at the art school,
I liked a girl too.
But until
my dad forced me to drop out,
I never had the courage to tell her.
Shen Xi
is the second girl I've ever liked.
That's nice.
If you behave well,
I might consider giving you a chance
to be my brother-in-law.
Really?
Don't lie to me.
How will you help me?
Why would I lie to you?
But
you have to listen to me on this.
We can't rush it.
I'll talk to her first
and slowly
plant the idea.
Haste makes waste.
You know that, right?
I know.
I'm definitely not in a rush.
Eat.
You still remember this place.
Of course.
Even if you forget, I never will.
Never will?
If you won't, why didn't you come to me
when you returned?
Is it because of what happened to Uncle?
You still can't get over it.
If I couldn't get over it,
I wouldn't have come back here.
You've been hiding from me, Song Yanfei.
What are you hiding from?
Li Xingchen: Yu Xiaotong
Song Yanfei: Wang Zhiyong (Wang Ruizi)
Shen Xi: Xie Tiantian
Special Appearance
(in order of strokes of Chinese surname)
Xiao Ze: Wang Hao
Jiang Dahai: Liu Zheting (Liu Zheting)
Mu Liyan: Chen Yongxia
Weng Wei: Huang Fei (Huang Jingxin)
Gao Yuhai: Cao Haitao (Cao Jingshi)
Trace Evidence Police: Kang Hairu
Li Xingchen's Classmate
Zha Minxin
Extras
Xiao Ze's Mother: Zhao Yue'en
Xiao Ze's Relatives: Li Ming, Wang Zhilei
Assistant: Bai Zhihao
Dancers: Liu Yuxin, Yang Jiayue
Li Xingchen's Mother: Dong Dong
Female Classmate: Yue Yue
Li Xingchen's Classmates:
Tang Tang, Dai Guoming
Secretary: Qian Duoduo
Dai Mu: Wang Chunyang
Xia Youzhen
Fengshu's Secretary: Dai Dai
Liu Haohan
Liu Ran
Waiters: Liu Jiaqi, Dai Guoming
Aunties: Tu Manxia, Huang Xinyang
Middle-aged Man: Wang Xinda
Driver Zhao: Wei Hong
Surveillance Police: Qin Zhiqiang
Xiao Ze's Father: Zhou Wen
Stagehand Zhang: Li Chen
Speaking Girl: Yue Yue
Police Colleague: Li Lijun
Receptionist Teacher: Ren Jiefei
Mr. Zhao: Liu Junjie
Driver: Hu Huazheng
Scrapyard Boss Zhang: Li Chenghu
Crane Operator: Liu Haitao
Yan's Father: Li Tianjun
Male Doctor: Wang Keming
Bai Wanting
Speaking Contestant
Bai Xiaosi's Stand-in: Zhao
Cashier: Wu Tiantian
Forensic Doctor Zhou Wen: Pei Xiao
Cleaner: Liu Li
Extras: Da Qing, Liu Haohan
Receptionist Xiaoyu: Ren Jiefei
Chief Presenter: Xu Yue
Presenters: Sui Dalong, Yu Tianhang
Co-Presenters: Feng Fei, Guo Zhiyuan
Chief Planner: Li Meina
Consultant: Bai Di
Production Team
Hu Kaichen
Planner: Zhao
Yin Zhongheng
Line Producer: Hu Huazheng
Finance: Geng Yusa
Stage Management Team
Stage Management Leader: Liu Yiqing
Yang Qunbao
Kitchen
Kitchen Manager: Yin Xiumei
Li Zhiwei, Ma Yuan
Zhang Meijuan, Zheng Xiaorong
Zhang Kai, Liang Hui
Li Xiaojun, Song Shuwei
Hu Lei, Qiao Xueyue
Xiao Yucai
Co-Director Xu Yue
Assistant Directors Tang Yuye, Li Gaoyang
On-Set Deputy Director
Casting Director Dai Guoming
Editing Team
Sound Director Zhang Kai
Co-Art Director Gong Xueyuan
Prop Art Zhang Xueqi
Props Wu Tai
On-Set Supervisor Hou Yonghao
Prop Set Dressers
Zhang Li, Zhang Qingzhong
Camera A Operator He Yong
Camera A Assistant Li Xinghan
Camera B Operator Zhao Shidian
Camera C Operator Ma Mingguo
Lighting Team
Lighting Director Gao Yun
Terigun
Styling Team
Styling Director Gao Bin
On-Set Hair & Makeup Supervisor Li Zixu
On-Set Wardrobe
Zhang Tingting, Qiu Yaqiong
Promotion & Distribution Team
Marketing Director Li Yiyi
Planning Director Yang Liuting
Project Coordinator Zhao Zihan
Copywriters Zhang Weirui, Li Ziwei
Graphic Designers Ren Zhongjun, Shi Qi
Post-Production Supervisor
Colorist Niu Xue
End Credits Jin Linxin
Re-recording Mixer Zhang Kai
Sound Effects Editor Zhang Xiaoman
Visual Effects
Jin Linxin